

About me

Full-stack developer with more than 5 years of experience creating web and mobile solutions with React, React Native, Node.js, PHP and ASP .NET. Specialist in relational databases and not relational, and design patterns.

Committed to the delivery of scalable, efficient and well-documented products.

PERSONAL DETAILS

• Ciudad Victoria, Tamulipas

josuenolan96@gmail.com

+52 834 252 32 84

Josué Isaí Nolasco Quintero

Developer

Experience

Secretariado Ejecutivo del Sistema Estatal de Seguridad Pública Tamaulipas

DESARROLLADOR Mar 2020 - Presente

I led the development of web, mobile and desktop systems for internal control, administration, and monitoring processes using React, Node.js and SQL Server. I reduced the times of 40% processing through automation of key processes.

Smart City Soft

Developer Apr 2023 - Feb 2024

I participated in the development of the platform Ventanila Única" using React, MUI Material, Node and Mongoose. I optimized user flows and helped scale the system for more than 10 municipal governments in Mexico.

Education

Instituto Tecnológico de Ciudad Victoria

Computer Systems Engineering

Aug 2014 - Feb 2019

Skills summary

Frontend

React |S React Native Expo

HTML CSS Tailwind CSS

MUI Material ShadCN/UI Zustand

Tanstack React Query React Hook Form Zod

Backend

Typescript Node Express
Passport Sequelize Mongoose

C# ASP .NET PHP

Laravel

Databases

MySQL SQL Server Postgres SQL

MongoDB

Other skills

Git Docker JWT

REST APIs

Languages

English B1

In the process of improvement